



+55 47 99604-8141





oscaryopan.netlify.app



São José, SC - BR

ABOUT ME

I have been working in another area for the last 11 years, but that was never my dream and that was an a frustation for me. Since I discover the developing, I feel mysel realized, in many times during my studies and pratices, feel not working or studing, I'm having fun! And now I'm looking for an opportunity to enter this wonderful area, programming.

SKILLS

HTML CSS JavaScript React JS

Git / Github



EXPERIENCES

Copy Line LTDA 2017 - 2023

PRINTER TECHNICIAN

Maintenance of Copy Machines and Printers of different brands.

Konica Minolta Business Solutions BR 2013 - 2017 PRINTER TECHNICIAN

Konica Minolta Specialist Copier and Printer Maintenance.

Dominy Climatização 2012 - 2013

TECHNICIAN SUPPORT

Corrective maintenance and installation of air conditioning, of various brands and models.

Maschall Copiadoras LTDA 2009 - 2012 PRINTER TECHNICIAN

Maintenance of Copy Machines and Printers of different brands.

EDUCATION

2023 - In Progress

UDEMY

Vocational course Learning JavaScript, TypeScript, ReactJS, NextJS, Styled-Components, Testing with Jest, Storybook, Strapi

JavaScript / React JS etc. Teacher: Luiz Otávio Miranda.

2022 Curso em Video

HTML / CSS

Vocational course Basic to advanced HTML5 and CSS3 course, with an introduction to JavaScript. Teacher: Gustavo Guanabara.

2019 **IFSC**

PUBLIC MANAGEMENT

Undegraduate degree in Public Management at the Federal Institute of Santa Catarina (IFSC).

2002

CEFET-SC

High School d Degree

High School degree at the Centro Federal de Educação tecnológica do Estado de Santa Catarina, with Electrotechnical Specialization.